sup everyone cameras wanted to [ __ ] you
with a very very very special video as
you can see before me got this boxing
right here on the table now you're not
gonna believe this [ __ ] just just now
while I was cleaning out my garage found
this box just hidden behind a bunch of
other John boxes and I was like to throw
it away just think it was a random box
or some [ __ ] although when I open it you
are not gonna believe that the [ __ ]
that's in it I mean let's just say wet
when I opened it I myself almost [ __ ] my
pants I mean I mean mostly because
inside of it is well no no no [ __ ] no
I'll open it so you can see for yourself
oh yes look at that everyone this isn't
my very own Sonic on our comic book
series that I made when I was just a
little kid when talking was still on TV
what some would say when God was she on
her look at this [ __ ] in one I musta
made like oh my God oh oh yes all that
mmm I must have made like I don't know I
must be like a hundred comics or soul
can't believe this [ __ ] I'll bring it
over here so you can see it in a lot
better as you can see all the Sonic
Sonia Mannix leads think that's sweet
but I don't know I don't really know who
that is but as you can see sock on the
ground episode 1 their journey begins
fellow joins the team guess that's fair
then okay that's kind of cool look at
this [ __ ] boom look at that can you
believe I that kids yeah everybody what
you're seeing right here is the way I
used to draw sama is Sonia as a [ __ ]
Navy God I must have drawn us me like
5-10 years ago I don't give a [ __ ] oh no
oh no oh my God look at that everyone
one two three four five six seven I need
you 77 [ __ ] pay to finish it this is
insane look at that oh my God me too
episode three so far so 500 this Mindy
oh all right that's kind of cool [ __ ]
damn this um I want to show us up my ass
that you [ __ ] are notice here in this
coin your entire life have you [ __ ]
oh my God look at that Uncle Chuck joins
a team mmm no there's Uncle Chuck
[ __ ] mmm this is the coolest [ __ ] you
know I may just do a video on this I I
mean this is a hundred this is a hundred
week's worth of videos right here for
one I could like review every single one
shove it up my ass oh damn everyone look
at that can you believe I do I do all of
these ah I'm surprising myself holy [ __ ]
this is insane look at this oh my God
mmm
come on can't live this [ __ ] come on mmm
oh yeah Bobby a cute little sue oh
there's a couple of badasses over there
in the corner [ __ ] k everyone I got
the comics out of the box let's see the
goods find out which one looks good we
got up so one cups of two three four
five I want to see this one what we see
them with Nene how about that [ __ ]
look at that oh oh this is the sexy
[ __ ] sock on sock on dad asks oh my God
okay well this I got Mindy oh then this
is gonna turn to your sex scene isn't it
[ __ ] that's a good [ __ ] wait all
there with yet money's just like I guess
they get to me to their lives or for
let's say let's see oh yeah oh [ __ ] that
is not the same that is not the same
care then that is [ __ ] that is that
is little [ __ ] oh my God she she
[ __ ] changes every picture oh my God
oh look a look at that [ __ ] oh that's a
good [ __ ] out there ok now let's get
there go on I mean this has got be good
at Mindy shooting Manic in the ass Sonic
jump me the corner had a TV um-hmm uh no
I don't know what oh [ __ ] Oh
[ __ ] oh oh oh oh [ __ ] oh my God this is
[ __ ] uh-uh what the [ __ ] Sonia what
did you do she did not deserve this [ __ ]
oh my God this is this is [ __ ] insane
oh oh no oh ball bead in trouble lady
Windermere oh my God it's Bob acts like
a sexy ass [ __ ] how delightful oh my
God look at this look at the [ __ ]
everyone can you believe this [ __ ] I do
all of this [ __ ] oh how did I jaundice
jaja one comic a day down this is insane
oh my God oh oh oh oh [ __ ] what is that
that is [ __ ] ah oh my God like I gotta
see that I got I got check must checking
myself like an even allow on youtube cuz
it [ __ ] that it could be firewood man
well it looks like on the cover
come on okay everyone I guess it's not
nearly as bad as it is on the cover just
cuz it's just that you like this Athair
looking at his ass outside air oh oh oh
oh God its head oh oh [ __ ] oh my God oh
oh [ __ ] oh oh my God me too Marik Vito I
know it I I know what you mean Manic I
don't know if I should make this Joe
kind of [ __ ] up a Manic on dad ass am
i right boo days [ __ ] the hug you know
what no no I should not show this comic
anymore it shouldn't be allowing you to
would kind of [ __ ] up so yeah that's
pretty much it [ __ ] I just read
through some of these comments myself
and I'm not gonna bother Stewie it's
actually pretty I'm good especially the
second half I'm the first half yeah it
does have a little bit slow but really
what series doesn't anybody I'm just
look at the cover but look at the colors
look days that is that dips are one it's
kind of cool but of course on a blinded
will although if you go like just 16
times less you chapter 17 look at that
that is intent as far like Sonya buckles
when the one right after that we could
see what I think is Sonic matting
involve your bosses the next one after
that get to see song again like
exploding some [ __ ] I don't know I have
to read this ditch I'm I will got catch
for my own comic series kind kind of
cool if you ask me just want to shovel
mine anyway yeah so let me know down the
cards if you want me to actually review
it on my new channel or even better
I could I could do I don't know I can't
do a lot of Raksha me reading every
single one like like look at this one
this one is is a [ __ ] movie so yeah
let me know oh my God mmm that is cute i
love it too let me know if you want me
to read it on youtube channel don't
forget to comment rate subscribe new
video will be up in a few days about our
Kenzie it's gonna be bitchin [ __ ]
boom